A Witch
Celina would never...
Of course not. It would be impossible
for her, living out in Verun.
But if Keiren says so,
suspicion may very well fall on her.
What?!
That's the government-general for you,
and Keiren wields considerable power there.
Is there nothing we can do?!
Acting thoughtlessly could get us
accused of overstepping our bounds.
There's something else
I'm worried about, too.
I have brought her, Lady Keiren.
Welcome to Galoa.
You must be Celina. Thank you
for making the long journey.
And you are...?
Dolan, of Verun Village.
I took it upon myself to accompany her.
Is that so?
Welcome.
I'm sure you're hungry.
Let us have dinner first.
Gouda, please go on ahead
and draft up your report.
Understood.
Wow, this looks delicious.
Feel free to have whatever you like.
Call it making up for summoning you here.
You must have been concerned.
Thank you. I'll do just that.
We appreciate it.
But if Celina intends to
continue living in Verun,
she would've had to come
to Galoa at some point.
That's right. I'll get the
paperwork started tomorrow.
I'm so relieved.
I was shocked when all those
soldiers showed up out of nowhere.
I thought I was going to be killed.
That was certainly a possibility.
There were concerns you were manipulating
the villagers with your cursed eyes.
But I see they were misplaced.
I would never have you eliminated
when you're so pure and beautiful.
That was quicker than expected.
Why are you here?
Where are Dolan and Celina?!
I need to speak with the
headmistress, you see.
I hope you like the food.
Yes. It's delicious.
Really? I'm glad to hear it.
I've seen many a lamia in my time,
but you're strikingly beautiful.
Your pretty hair, you clear
blue eyes, and your scales...
I almost want to eat you up.
Huh?
Do you mind if I tell her?
It's not like we have a choice.
Have you heard of the recent incidents
of young women disappearing in Galoa?
I have, yes. And that not a
single one of them has been found.
What does that have to do with Celina?
There happens to be a mage living in Galoa.
She is said to be over 300 years old.
The headmistress?!
Not me.
She is human, and humans
don't live that long.
You suspect she's using forbidden magic?
The academy's top student is
no slouch, I see. Exactly.
They say she used forbidden magic
to possess a young woman's body
and continue living.
And now, that mage has taken
an interest in a lamia.
Celina!
We don't have time.
We should head there at once.
I'll fill you in on the way.
Is that all right?
Sheesh. I didn't want to get
a student involved in this.
I haven't got my hands on
a live lamia in forever.
Not to mention one that is so full of life.
Such pretty skin, and it will soon be mine!
I should skin her first and
think about my next move later.
Don't touch Celina.
Did I mess up the dosage?
Hm, the magic circle on the floor...
It reeks of blood.
This must be routine for you.
How many people have you killed?
Those restraints were made
with gollum lizard skin.
Are you really human?
These people never listen, do they?
I'll ask again. How many
people have you killed?
Beats me. I stopped
counting after a hundred.
And why did you kill them?
Research.
Everyone possesses something
beautiful, right?
So I collected them all for myself.
That's what keeps me so beautiful.
That magic should be forbidden.
Did you make a deal with a devil?
I did.
I got these arms from an arachne,
and my legs from beastkin.
This elf skin is oh so pretty too, isn't it?
But I think it's about
time I got an upgrade.
Your desires take precedence
over the lives of others?
How depraved can you be?
You don't appreciate my beauty?
I feel sorry for you.
My research has been recognized
by many powerful people.
Rejoice. This girl has passed my eye test.
I'll use every last bit of her.
No part of her will go to waste.
Is that all?
You did such cruel things just for that?!
You're awake, too?
That drug needs to be improved.
Did you trick that arachne, beastkin, and elf
just like you did me?!
They all must've come to
you looking for help!
So what?
They were doomed to a life of struggle,
sure to ruin their lovely skin
in the pleasure quarters.
They should thank me for
putting it to much better use.
How awful. Commissioner Gouda
was right about you.
Gouda? Why would he...
The thing about scoundrels is that
they always come with a big mouth.
This is a magic item that transmits sound.
Gouda has heard about all your evil deeds!
Are you two all right?!
What a showy entrance...
Celina, Dolan!
You're okay?!
I could scarcely believe my ears when
I heard you took on the role of bait!
We apologize for dragging you into this.
Apprehend Keiren!
Sire!
I take it you were going to frame
Celina for the kidnappings
and report that you had to kill
her because she resisted.
Then you could use her body
however you pleased.
Was that your scheme?
You would stoop to murder
if it kept you alive?
It's scarcely believable.
Talking down to me from up
on your high horse, eh?
You were blessed with pretty faces,
so you would never understand
how much I struggled to
obtain this beauty of mine.
There is so much beauty in this world.
It fascinated me in my youth.
But soon, I realized
that I was not part of it.
Give it to me.
Give me more.
More...
More!
I can do it!
I can be far more beautiful!
I was going to be!
You vain high elves.
How dare you talk down to
me and belittle my efforts?!
I'll show you the fruits of my
300 years of research!
Hand over that lamia!
What in the world?!
It's body fusion.
She's put together parts of
various species with magic.
Is that even possible?!
You really did make a deal with a devil.
How many lives were sacrificed
to make this possible?
Look how big and beautiful I am,
made up with countless lives!
I will live forever in harmony
with all manner of living beings!
Congratulations! You will
become part of my beauty, too!
Damn it! No!
Keep away!
Halt!
The lamia's cursed eyes? Such power!
Get away now!
Hurting my friends is a
crime punishable by death.
Let's go, El Spada!
It hurts...
How dare you hurt my legs... my body!
Eg de Aster!
Dark magic.
She lives up to her reputation.
Such powerful offensive magic.
This is no time to be impressed.
We need to do something.
But I can't summon spirits underground.
We'll all end up buried alive.
Okay.
Celina, Christina, I'll take it from here.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Using a superior magic now?
There's another magic circle, too.
Ah, he plans to use a barrier
magic while attacking.
Hey, mage.
Let me ask you something.
Are you happy now?
Don't look at me like that!
Behold my mana! I have long
surpassed human limits!
You will all recognize and
kneel before my beauty!
Bloodstained hands can
never obtain true beauty!
Those bodies you absorbed belonged to those
with hopes and dreams for the future!
They were not meant to be
consumed by the likes of you!
Celestial Javelins!
Dolan!
Er, um... I...
Shall we take a break?
My head's about to explode!
Studying is terrifying!
It proves that you're getting used to it.
You must be able to express your
thoughts in the language of this land.
I can't wait to see what you will write.
It's all because I used my cursed eyes.
Even you're having to stay confined
in this mansion with me.
Don't let it bother you.
Well? Make any progress?
My head's spinning!
So she says, but she can
read a fair bit now.
I see. You must be a good teacher.
He is, but I'm more impressed
that you can do this every day.
Oh, Headmistress Olivia and...
Commissioner Gouda!
I must say...
Apologies for not coming by sooner.
You must be busy with the aftermath.
It's understandable.
I'm truly sorry for getting you
involved in that incident.
Please raise your head!
We ended up just fine!
I was very surprised when you suggested
we act as bait to investigate.
I feel terrible for putting
you through that.
We were fine thanks to the
antidote Master gave me.
It counteracted Keiren's drug immediately.
The government-general is ashamed that
it let its own mage commit such crimes.
Oh, I nearly forgot.
I brought this for you.
Is that...
The first one is your permit for Galoa.
And the second is your registration.
Rest assured you'll be able to
live in Verun without issue.
Hooray!
We knew you were a gentle
soul from the start, Celina.
My apologies for keeping
you waiting so long.
He's so different from the
first time we met him.
Indeed. He's hard to dislike.
By the way, there is someone
who wishes to meet you.
It's been a while, Dolan.
I never expected to see you in Galoa.
It has, Denzel. This is...
N-Nice to meet you! I'm Celina.
So you're the one. My mother
spoke of you in her letters.
Denzel is old Maguru's son.
The headmistress has told me
all about your exploits.
Since you're here,
why don't we take a stroll of
the city? I'll show you around.
This is the main street.
You can find basically anything here.
Wow, this is amazing!
Yay!
A lamia?!
Come here! She's dangerous!
No way!
Dolan...
Let's buy gifts for the
villagers and head back.
Yeah.
Let's buy lots and surprise them all.
I'll give this back for you.
Right.
Thank you all for everything.
Likewise. I really appreciate
your assistance.
Don't mention it. You should come
home to Verun sometime, Denzel.
I will.
Dolan.
Would you like to join the academy?
The headmistress and I spoke earlier.
Your magic powers are extraordinary.
It would be a shame to let them go to waste.
I appreciate the invitation,
but I have my hands full with my
own affairs and the village's.
I see. But take your time
and think about it.
Your soul...
If you wish to use those
powers to help people,
I believe you'll need to expand
your knowledge at the academy.
If you want to protect the village you love,
leaving it might be one way to do it.
I suppose so.
See you. Safe travels.
Are you considering what the
headmistress said to you?
Yes. I can't say I'm not intrigued
by the magic academy,
but I feel like I have much
to do in the village yet.
You truly do love your village.
Verun certainly is a lovely place.
Seeing Galoa has emphasized that Verun is a
remote, tiny place with little to offer.
What do you think, Christina?
We're not far apart in age. Call me Chris.
Sure. What do you think, Chris?
Certainly.
There's only so much you can
learn in Verun Village.
And the academy will afford you
experiences you will not find here.
Hm...
Maybe Denzel is right. Going to the
academy might be a good option.
Wh-What is this?!
Next Episode
This week's lucky item is a picture book!
Look forward to next time!